highways.gov.uk 2008-12-17

# Highways Agency - Privacy Statement

### Respecting your privacy

Unless otherwise stated, the Highways Agency web site does not automatically store or capture personal information.

On occasions where personal information is requested, users will be informed about how their personal details will be used and how long this information will be retained for. In all cases, unless clearly stated otherwise, personal information will not be used for any other purpose.

The system will record your e-mail address and other information only if volunteered to us by you. This shall be treated as proprietary and confidential. It may be used for internal review or to notify you about updates to the Highways Agency web site.

We do not use cookies, and we will not collect any information about you except as outlined above.

This privacy statement only covers the Highways Agency web site at [http://www.highways.gov.uk](http://www.highways.gov.uk/). Links within this site to other web sites are not covered by this statement.

If you want to know whether any information is held about you, please see our policy under the [Data Protection Act 1998.](http://www.highways.gov.uk/foiresponses/2292.aspx)

### Electronic Surveys and Personal Information

The Highways Agency occasionally operates electronic surveys on our website, sometimes in conjunction with our contractors. The information you provide will be kept in a secure environment only accessible by the Highways Agency and the specific contractor(s) working with us on that project. 

The information you submit will only be used for the purpose specified in the survey. Personal details are collected only to ensure entries are not duplicated and in order to contact respondents and any potential prize winners if necessary. All personal details will be deleted at the end of the survey analysis period unless otherwise stated. 

Your personal information will not be shared with any other individuals or organisations unless otherwise stated.
